[{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678909630,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":34569,"timeElapsed":103978},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678924116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":14485,"timeElapsed":118463},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678933060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8943,"timeElapsed":127408},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678940239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":7178,"timeElapsed":134586},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678945029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4790,"timeElapsed":139377},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678956216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":11185,"timeElapsed":150564},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678960657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4440,"timeElapsed":155005},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678972789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":12132,"timeElapsed":167137},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678981612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"104","question":"Are you religious or spiritual? What kind of religious or spiritual beliefs do you have, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8822,"timeElapsed":175960},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678990807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":8222,"timeElapsed":185154},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678997776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":6968,"timeElapsed":192123},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679003324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5547,"timeElapsed":197672},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008102,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4777,"timeElapsed":202450},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679012346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4244,"timeElapsed":206694},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679021322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8974,"timeElapsed":215670},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025376,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4054,"timeElapsed":219724},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":8529,"timeElapsed":228254},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"60","question":"What belief or value have you completely changed your mind about over the years?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2753,"timeElapsed":231007},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":9689,"timeElapsed":242160},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679052603,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4789,"timeElapsed":246951},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":5425,"timeElapsed":252376},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063345,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":5316,"timeElapsed":257693},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077425,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":14079,"timeElapsed":271773},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679084661,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7235,"timeElapsed":279009},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679100358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":15696,"timeElapsed":294705},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679102801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2443,"timeElapsed":297149},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":7866,"timeElapsed":305016},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116891,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"200","question":"Do you have a favorite food or cuisine? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":6222,"timeElapsed":311238},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679140991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":23384,"timeElapsed":335338},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":5649,"timeElapsed":340989},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679152725,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":6083,"timeElapsed":347073},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158230,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":5504,"timeElapsed":352578},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3768,"timeElapsed":356347},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679167467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":5467,"timeElapsed":361815},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2557,"timeElapsed":364373},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7638,"timeElapsed":372012},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679186526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":8861,"timeElapsed":380874},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":10602,"timeElapsed":392301},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679204291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6337,"timeElapsed":398639},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679215296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11004,"timeElapsed":409644},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679219480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":413828},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6344,"timeElapsed":420173},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":9830,"timeElapsed":430004},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4709,"timeElapsed":434714},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":10276,"timeElapsed":444991},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679258472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":7828,"timeElapsed":452820},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679274735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":15347,"timeElapsed":469083},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679278863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4128,"timeElapsed":473211},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679284551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5687,"timeElapsed":478899},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":4880,"timeElapsed":483780},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679293087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":3654,"timeElapsed":487435},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679305682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":12594,"timeElapsed":500030},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679309276,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3593,"timeElapsed":503624},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679315708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6431,"timeElapsed":510056},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679320550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"86","question":"Who do you think is the most underrated artist, performer, or athlete?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4841,"timeElapsed":514898},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679332104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":10558,"timeElapsed":526452},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679338651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":6546,"timeElapsed":532999},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679342861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":4210,"timeElapsed":537209},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679346566,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":3704,"timeElapsed":540914},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679352880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6313,"timeElapsed":547228},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679360291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":7410,"timeElapsed":554639},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679366789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6498,"timeElapsed":561137},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679374331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7541,"timeElapsed":568679},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679381517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"40","question":"If you could visit your past self at a younger age and offer your past self advice about how to live your life (not just where to invest your money…), what would you say?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7185,"timeElapsed":575865},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679393360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":10467,"timeElapsed":587708},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679397001,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3640,"timeElapsed":591349},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679404123,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7121,"timeElapsed":598471},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679407776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3652,"timeElapsed":602124},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679415564,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":7787,"timeElapsed":609912},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679421076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":5511,"timeElapsed":615424},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679428354,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":7277,"timeElapsed":622702},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679431986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3631,"timeElapsed":626334},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679437758,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5771,"timeElapsed":632106},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679439618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"168","question":"What is your go-to breakfast when you are in a hurry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":1859,"timeElapsed":633966},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679453373,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":13062,"timeElapsed":647721},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679456806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3432,"timeElapsed":651154},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679467491,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":10684,"timeElapsed":661839},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679472488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":4996,"timeElapsed":666836},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679477577,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":5088,"timeElapsed":671925},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679485533,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7955,"timeElapsed":679881},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679489860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4326,"timeElapsed":684208},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679495171,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5310,"timeElapsed":689519},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679499087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3915,"timeElapsed":693435},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679509358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":9534,"timeElapsed":703706},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":706193},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679517535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":5689,"timeElapsed":711883},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679522986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5450,"timeElapsed":717334},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679526807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3821,"timeElapsed":721155},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679538578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":11770,"timeElapsed":732926},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541311,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2732,"timeElapsed":735659},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679548743,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7431,"timeElapsed":743091},{"subjectID":"b3um4dy2fd","prolificID":"6652c43d08992eba0cff0e80","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b444b0e20ec754a87cc","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679550589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1845,"timeElapsed":744937}]